(Amy:)I only used urban slang to sound tough
so people wouldn't break in.
(Sheldon:)It's not the message.
(Amy:)Well, what is it then?
I did everything just the way you like it.
- You did.
- Then what the hell, Sheldon?
(Amy:)We have been going out for over two years,
and I've been nothing but patient with you.
(Amy:)I watch your dopey space movies,
I signed your ridiculous contracts.
I stopped wearing lip gloss because
you said it made my mouth look slippery.
(Amy:)I am the best girlfriend
you're ever gonna have.
(Amy:)You give me one good reason
why I can't live here.
(Sheldon:)It's Penny's fault.
(Leonard:)- What?
- She doesn't wanna live with Leonard...
(Sheldon:)...so he has to come live here again.
She's the snake in our garden.
(Sheldon:)She's the reason we can't be happy.
(Amy:)- Hey, Ames.
- Yeah, "Hey, Ames" nothing.
(Amy:)I was all set to move in
with Sheldon and I can't because...
- ...you don't wanna live with Leonard.
- What?